Do you know why fairy tales only write about weddings?
Because after that, they have to be made into suspense films.
Guess who cheats first,
who is scheming to get property,
and who's "love you forever"
is the first to withdraw.
If you believe in love that ties interests,
you'll end up lining up and drawing numbers
between the Civil Affairs Bureau and the mental hospital.
Come on.
You come to me first.
It's rare to see.
How many shares
of Golden Thread do you have now?
Just enough to see.
As long as Lu Xu doesn't wake up,
I can still play a game
with Annie.
To play a game with Annie,
you really went all out.
Even a lion
uses all its strength to fight a rabbit.
Otherwise,
how can Xiao Chu and I
stand our ground in Shen Family?
That's your style.
But have you ever thought that
if you sail into the whirlpool
of Golden Thread without thinking,
you'll be smashed to pieces?
No risk, no gain.
Maybe
I can come back
in the whirlpool.
What about Jiang Li?
Is she your crew
or prey?
It depends on
her choice.
What do you think
she'll choose?
If she's a crew,
I hope you won't be stingy
after a full harvest.
But what if
she's just a prey?
I want to try.
A lion uses all its strength
to catch a rabbit.
I...
How far can I go?
I'll do as you say.
So,
how are you going to help me?
The live streaming room has reached a climax.
Now, a guest is about to appear.
Who do you think it will be?
That's right.
It's our female lead,
the eldest Miss of the Lu family,
Lu Qianqian.
Why are you here?
I really like this girl.
I wish you were my daughter-in-law.
I really like you.
Wen, let me introduce.
This is the person mom has been wanting to meet.
She is an internationally renowned designer,
Charles' most accomplished student, Jiang Li.
Hello.
What do you want?
Li Yiwen,
is this your third
Is this your third or fourth name?
Did you buy this with the money you took from Zhuang Wan?
What role are you playing this time?
A fallen heiress or a strong woman back from abroad?
Stop before it's too late.
I'm not the same Li Xiaorou I used to be.
You have nothing to threaten me with.
What if your future mother-in-law finds out
the child you're carrying isn't her son's?
How could you...
That's impossible.
Li Sisi's
mother died young.
She grew up with an alcoholic father.
She cut ties with her father as an adult.
She got into the School of Business Administration through her own efforts.
After graduation, she was full of hope.
But she faced workplace harassment.
She took her superior to court.
Although she won the lawsuit,
she suffered workplace bullying.
Then she changed her name to Li Xiaorou
[to start afresh.]
[She became Lu Qianqian's assistant.]
Zhou Jian was also arranged by you?
Your best friend Su Muchen asked you.
Who are you?
The sister who broke off contact with Su Muchen.
Su Muli.
My sister must have mentioned me to you.
Please let me go.
I didn't do anything.
I'm begging you,
please let me go.
I didn't set Zhou Jian up with Lu Qianqian,
and your sister's death has nothing to do with me.
The Lu family was like a mountain pressing down on me,
I had no choice but to pretend I knew nothing.
Indeed,
you didn't do anything before my sister died,
but as her best friend,
your cold indifference is just adding fuel to the fire.
You watched the Lu family drive her to death.
I'm sorry.
I had no choice.
What do I have to do to make you let me go?
Not everyone you say sorry to
will say it's okay.
You have to be punished for what you've done.
Give this USB drive to the media
the day before the release of Dark Fairy Tale.
Also do one thing at the press conference.
Use AI face swap to replace me in the live broadcast.
Where is Jiang Li?
Where is she?
She's so beautiful.
Oh my god.
Impossible.
Jiang Li.
Hello, everyone.
I'm Lu Xu's fiancée,
the chief designer of Dark Fairy Tale.
You must be curious
why I don't have scars on my cheeks.
Because the avenger
whose hands were stained with blood
is a chapter I wrote
for Dark Fairy Tale.
There's no prince offering a crystal shoe,
nor is there a wand that can erase scars.
We always expect a knight to slay a dragon,
but we forget that in the oldest fairy tales,
it's always the princess who tears through the thorns.
Dark fairy tales are not excuses to sink,
but tell all those who have been scratched by life,
you don't need to wait for redemption,
because you are the fire that can burn the prairie.
Dark fairy tales are golden threads,
the first step towards luxury series clothing.
And this series is prepared for you.
Okay.
Pleasure to cooperate.
How did you know I was in danger?
Because I couldn't get in touch with you,
my intuition told me you were in danger.
Jenny avoided the surveillance,
but the sentinel system of the electric car beside her
captured the whole process of your abduction.
How can you still smile?
You almost died just now,
do you know that?
If the Death God took me,
he would be afraid that hell would be expanded.
Dark Fairy Tale,
Is it really that important
in your revenge plan?
Actually, no one knows
Annie wants the company to go public.
But she doesn't have enough capital.
She needs financing.
On the one hand, she wants to raise funds,
on the other hand, she refuses to increase her sister-in-law's capital.
Isn't it contradictory?
She's afraid that Zhuang Wan has too much equity,
which will deprive her of the actual control of the company.
So she needs to find your grandfather,
a financial group that absolutely does not allow cooperation, to raise funds.
Morgan.
Right.
For Annie,
there is no financial group more suitable than Morgan.
In this way, Zhuang Wan
can be completely prevented from using the relationship of Shen Family.
And Dark Fairy Tale is her credential to Morgan.
How do you know all this?
Annie is so careful.
aren't you curious
why she would just let me
be Lu Xu's fiancée?
It is indeed a little strange.
Because there's a Valuation Adjustment Mechanism between Morgan and Annie.
If the first-day sales of Dark Fairy Tale reach 150 million,
Morgan will buy 20% of the shares in Annie's hands.
If not,
Morgan will convert the investment into a loan.
To convert equity into a loan,
without damaging the brand image,
so
she invited my teacher Charles to design this series.
And I volunteered to take over this matter.
So Dark Fairy Tale is the first step,
and also the most critical step.
But if the sales of Dark Fairy Tale do not meet expectations,
isn't that just what Annie wants?
No one knows
that Morgan and I also have a VAM.
Am I not good enough to you?
Why do you help Jiang Li?
You're using a small amount of money
to trample on my dignity as a human being.
Maybe
We define goodness differently.
I'm not doing this to help Jiang Li.
It's for the sake of the child in my belly.
You're pregnant?
It's Lu Xu's child.
I once tried to take your place in his heart.
But then I realized
I was just a substitute
after he lost you.
When I let go of all this,
I realized it was a relief.
I will tell my child in the future
that his father is a lovesick bastard.
Because he has the right to know who his father is.
And your child
also has the right to know who his father is.
What do you mean?
You can tell Mumu
that his father
is a jerk who is infatuated with his mother.
You guys came back so quietly.
Ms. Jiang,
madam is waiting for you inside.
Little Monster,
you're better at this than I thought.